managementparadise.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy on ManagementParadise.com

  | 

ManagementParadise.com (MP) hereby declares its privacy policy with regard to different features available, services offered and the mode of operation involving the data storage, tracing, and management techniques involved in the operation of its web portal. 

The said Policy is formulated under the terms of service. Keeping in mind the utmost importance of a user’s privacy, MP shall endeavor to make sure that any information provided by any user is not misused in any manner whatsoever.    
**FEATURES OF THE POLICY  **   
_**A. Information Collection**_   
Any private or personal information collected on the portal is affected by this privacy policy. Users provide for information when:   
Visiting the website. Account is opened/ Account registration. Filling of Profile Details. Adding of Contacts Using various services provided by MP like chat, blog, survey, projects and various others. All the data or information submitted by the user is saved by MP in a database named manageme_nilesh with a Localhost via UNIX socket server which maintains all the information submitted by the user or non-user in log files.   
Visitor logs are stored in the database for a temporary time. They are deleted once user is logged out or time expires if same user does not make any activity for more than 20 minutes.   
The information including their email id, IP address, current time and result of login efforts is collected in user logs for members and the same is limited to last 1000 logs whereas visitor’s log database is storing IP address, visitor’s browser info, user id, user name, and last activity time.   
User passwords are stored in an encrypted form by using the MD5 Hash Function.   
The web application provides for the number of members and non-members on all website pages as a header through the database.   
MP also makes use of cookies to store information pre as well as post signing in. These cookies store the last visiting time, last activity time, language id, login id, password and session id in encrypted form in cookies file of pre and post login as whatever the case might be.   
Mp stores server details in session variables irrespective whether the user is logged in or not. The information related to number of hits made by user when on website, starting and end time of current request and the time taken to process the current request, last activity time with reference to browser and update of log files, user id for reference of current user’s session, email and password in encrypted form, and time threshold to continue activity on the interface in their respective session variables, the details of which is not provided for security reasons.   
MP provides a unique system of prompting a user to login again if no activity is made for 20 minutes and states that it is intended for security purposes and shall be in no way violation of user privacy.   
MP assures that information stored by the users shall be available to other users in accordance with choice exercised by any such user while making of the profile or anytime after that. A user has all the rights to amend or modify information relating to him and to choose how much of that information shall be available to all the users generally.   
All users shall agree to provide the basic information needed to open an account and the same will be available to all other users. All users shall be free to choose their privacy settings and MP shall act upon it / manage it accordingly.    
_**B. Use of Information**_   
MP is a dynamic web portal dedicated to management students where they can connect, network, discuss, debate, ask for help regarding jobs and projects, conduct surveys and help others. The information submitted by users to MP is exclusively managed by MP.   
MP shall send notifications to all its users regarding the interaction occurring in their account on the recent updates feature depending upon the choice exercised by the user.   
MP shall reserve the rights regarding all personal information provided by the users and shall be the exclusive manager of all such information like bith date, education, and experience and address details.   
All the communities started by any user will be available to all the users to view and request joining or in accordance with the choice exercised by the maker of such community.   
Any personal information provided on articles/blogs/community by the user shall be at his own discretion and MP shall not be liable for, any such information being open to other users, any misuse of the same.   
All users warrant that they will not indulge in any making any fake profiles, data theft, unauthorized access or the likewise and shall be solely liable for any contravention.   
MP shall not be liable for any comments or remarks made by the users on any institution page whether claimed or unclaimed.   
MP does not guarantee the authenticity of any event whether featured or not posted by a user and the user shall be exclusively liable for any dispute if so arises.   
Information provided under any survey between a user and a user or corporate will solely at their discretion and MP not responsible in any manner whatsoever.   
MP has all rights to disclose any information provided by the user when required by law or during any company restructuring.   
MP has all rights to use the information provided by users for advertisement purposes.     
_**C. Information Choices    **_      
         If any service asks for sharing of personal information of the user, MP ensures that it will be notified to users at the time of availing of such services and the users       will be asked for their consent.   
Users can anytime review, update and make changes to their personal information and any old information will not be saved by MP in any kind of cache/backup.   
MP states that in few services an additional plug-in flash player might be required.   
Users are free to close their account at any time and the same can be done by selecting the deactivate account option in profile settings. The deactivation shall be acted upon by MP promptly and all the information about the user who chooses to close his account will be deleted from the database of MP. MP cannot be made liable for any sudden shut down of account by any user and for any loss arising out to anyone in whatsoever manner possible.    
_**D. User Obligations**_   
All users shall respect the privacy of each other and shall not involve themselves in any activity of any kind which might be invasive of other user’s privacy unless he/she is authorized to do so under a written consent by the user.   
Users shall respect all the intellectual property rights belonging to MP or any other third party.   
Users must not provide any information which can be injurious, offensive, racist, defamatory information be it related to any other user or oneself.   
MP reserves the right to take any appropriate action against any contravention by any user.    
_**CHANGES TO THE POLICY**_   
MP reserves the right to amend, modify or add any other term in the said policy about which the user shall be informed by an e-mail or notification on the home page of the web portal itself. The user, continuing to operate post such changes shall deemed to have accepted the new or changed terms.    
_**SECURITY AND ENFORCEMENT**_   
MP ensures to take appropriate security measures to protect against any unauthorized access or data manipulation or unwarranted disclosure.   
Users can contact us on [[email protected]](http://www.managementparadise.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
